Guide to the University Faculty records, 1909-1998.
University Faculty records, 1909-1998
- Series I. Dean of the Faculty Records (11-1)
  - Collection 11-1-1175 (Box 1-7)
    - Faculty Meetings - Work Papers and Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, Fall 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, Spring 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, Fall 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, Spring 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, Fall 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, Spring 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Council Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Council Work Papers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Council Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Academic Affairs, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Academic Affairs, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Academic Affairs sub committee on Admissions, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Research Policy and Personnel, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Research Policy and Personnel, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Faculty-Student Administrative Forum, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Faculty-Student Administrative Forum, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - General Legislation Work Papers, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - General Legislation Work Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Grades, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Grading, 1955-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Grading, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Hull Memorial Publication Fund, 1955-1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Human Rights Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Human Rights Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - International Student Affairs, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Lectures, Committee on, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Long Range Planning, Committee on, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Planning, Committee on, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Long Range Planning, Committee on, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Long Range Planning, Committee on, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Long Range Planning, Committee on, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Membership, Committee on, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Music, Committee on, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Music, Committee on, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Necrology of the Faculty - Work Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Nominations, Committee on, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Prizes, Committee on, 1956-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Registration & Schedules, Committee on, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Requirements for Graduation, Committee on, 1962-1964, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Scheduling of Public Events, Committee on, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Student Affairs - Annual Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - General, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      - Academic Actions, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
      - Academic Advising (Box 4)
      - Advisors to Stu. Organ., 1963 (Box 4)
      - Appearance of Students, 1965 (Box 4)
      - Band Uniforms, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Cornell Attrition, 1964 (Box 4)
      - Course Credit, 1964 (Box 4)
      - Curfews - Women, 1962-1964 (Box 4)
      - Discussion Group Fees, 1964 (Box 4)
      - Excuses from Classes, 1962 (Box 4)
      - Fac. Com-Student Repr., 1960-1963 (Box 4)
      - Fraternities, 1962 (Box 4)
      - Fraternities, 1962-1964 (Box 4)
      - Freshmen Orient. & Yr. (Box 4)
      - Grad. Res. Assts. -Tax, 1964 (Box 4)
      - Honor Societies, 1965 (Box 4)
      - Inter-Frat. Seminar Council, 1965 (Box 4)
      - J.F. Kennedy Scholarship, 1965 (Box 4)
      - Men's Residential Coun., 1964 (Box 4)
      - Medical Program, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Policy Statement, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Reg. Fee Student Activities, 1962 (Box 4)
      - Student Code, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
      - Students for Education, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      - Student-Faculty Relations, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Student Government Annual Award, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Student Government Annual Award, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
      - Student Government Annual Award, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
      - Student Government Annual Award, 1964-1965 (Box 4)
      - Student Government Annual Award, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
      - Student Government Records, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Spring Weekend, 1963 (Box 4)
      - Spring Day, 1965 (Box 4)
      - Student Transcripts, 1964 (Box 4)
      - Study Judicial System - Prior, 1962 (Box 4)
      - Willard Straight, 1960-1963 (Box 4)
      - Witholding Degrees, 1960 (Box 4)
    - University Press Board of Editors, 1952-1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Arts and Sciences Study - Dean Brown, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Appendices to Dean Brown's Report, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - CAL Work Papers, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - CAL Work Papers continued, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Center for Advancement of Education (Larson Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Draft Status of Students - Work Papers, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Long Range Planning Committee - Centennial Planning, March 21, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Quality of Undergraduate Instruction - File #1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Quality of Undergraduate Instruction - File #2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Student-Faculty Relationships (Kahn-Bowers Report) Work Papers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Dean's Retreat, April 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dean's Conference, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dean's Conference, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - President's Retreat, September 8, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - President's Retreat, December 11, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - President's Retreat, February 8, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - President's Retreat, June 7, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 1966-1967, July - January (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 1966-1967, February - June (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Secretary of Faculty Work Papers - P.P. Van Riper #1 - Com. on Memb. & Handbook (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Secretary of Faculty Work Papers - P.P. Van Riper #2 - Fac. Council, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Secretary of Faculty Work Papers - P.P. Van Riper #3 - Fac. Council, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Secretary of Faculty Work Papers - P.P. Van Riper #4 - Fac. Council, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Secretary of Faculty Work Papers - P.P. Van Riper #5 - Univ. Fac., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Secretary of Faculty Work Papers - P.P. Van Riper #6 - Univ. Fac., Spring 1962 - 1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure Committee Minutes - Notebook, 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Information (Notebook, prior Faculty Handbook), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Sindler Commission Documents (Box 7)
  - Collection 11-1-1272 (Box 1-3)
    - Academic Integrity, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Arts, Committee on - Memo from H. Peter Kahn, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Arts, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Budgets, work papers, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Budgets, work papers, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Committees, General, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - CURW, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Elections, Committee on, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Extra Mural and Summer Session, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Council Minutes - draft copies, January 1966 - May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Council Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Council Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Mailing List, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Mailing List, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Academic Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Public Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Council Committee on Researcy Policy and Personnel, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Minutes - draft copies, April 1966 - May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Minutes and Meetings - work papers, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Minutes and Meetings - work papers, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Fraternities, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Fraternities, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Fire - Cornell Residential Club (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - General Legislation of Faculty - work papers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Identification Cards, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - International Studies, Center for, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - International Studies, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Lectures, University Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Music, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Necrology of the Faculty, work papers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Nominations, Committee on - work papers, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Nominations, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Registration and Schedules, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Undergraduate Education, Commission on - Kahn-Bowers work papers (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Undergraduate Education, Requests for (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Long Range Planning, Background Material - blue hard binder (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Disciplinary Records - primarily Appeals to the Faculty Council, Student Conduct, Academic Integrity, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
  - Collection 11-1-1371 (Box 1)
    - Academic Freedom & Tenure, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom & Tenure, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Academic Integrity, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Values, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cornell Children's Tuition, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Extra Mural & S.S., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Appointments, etc., 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Council, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Meetings (work papers), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Financial Aid, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - General Legislation (work papers), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Human Rights, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Council Committee (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Academic Affairs, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
      - Public Affairs, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
      - Res. Pol. & Personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
    - International Student Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Necrology of Faculty (work papers), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Identification Cards, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Lectures, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Prize Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Nominating Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Nominating Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Nominating Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Nominating Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Collection 11-1-1415 (Box 1-6)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Judicial Procedures Committee (Jensen), 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Council Papers (Murphy), 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Council Papers (Miller), 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Some papers discussed at Exec. Staff Meetings (note: bulk of file destroyed as repetitious of President's files on Executive Staff Meetings and Retreats) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - The Kagan Resolution (Fraternities, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Some papers of R.P. Murphy (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "University Committees, Faculty Council", 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Crisis issues, etc. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Crisis papers (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Appointment Calendars, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - University Student Conduct Conference (USCC), 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - FCSA and The Judicial Crisis; FCSA (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Mailings, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Mailings, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Mailings, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Council Mailings, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Council Mailings, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council Mailings, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Council Mailings, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dean Hanson's Notebook (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom and Tenure, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Commission on ROTC (Kennedy) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Committee on ROTC (Ratner) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Committees, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Senate (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Black Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Student Government, 1958- (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - FCSA, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Barton Hall and Constitutent Assembly Investigation; Police Activities (Carton), Spring 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Recruting on Campus, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Willard Straight Affair - odds and ends (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Adjudicatory System, revision of, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Handbook 1968 edition (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - FCSA Minutes, Fall 1961 - September 30, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - (Box 4)
    - Academic Integrity, Committee on, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 2)
    - CURW File, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Council Minutes, 1967-1968 (Folder 5, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Council Minutes (Draft Copies), 1967-1968 (Folder 5)
    - Faculty Council Minutes (Draft Copies), 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Appointments, Resignations, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Mailing List, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Members, New, 1968 (Folder 5, Folder 10)
    - General Legislation, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 11)
    - General Legislation, 1969-1970 (Folder 5, Folder 12)
    - I.D. Card Requests, July 1, 1969 - June 30, 1970 (Folder 5, Folder 13)
    - International Student Affairs, Committee on, 1968-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 14)
    - Music Committee, 1967-1969 (Folder 5, Folder 15)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Volunteers, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Dean's Desk Calendars, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Declaration, Spring 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Necrology, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Petitions for President Perkins, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Registration and Schedules Minutes, 1946-1957 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ROTC Petitions, Spring 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Collection 11-1-1547 (Box 1-2)
    - Budget (one file), 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Budget (one file), 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Chronological (four files), July 1, 1969 - June 30, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, October 1, 1970 - December 31, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, July 1, 1970 - June 30, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - CIA Research Policy & Personnel (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Cornell United Religious Work, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Appointments, Resignations, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Council Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Council Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Council Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Council Statements, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Council Statements, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Council Draft Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Mailing List, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Council workpapers, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Council workpapers, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Faculty - New, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Faculty - Membership of, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Faculty - Membership of, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - I.D. Card Requests, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - I.D. Card Requests, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Award of Merit (United Fund) framed (Box 1)
    - Address to Edmund Ezra Day (several), 1950 (Box 2)
    - Prizes, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Resolution on University of California at Berkeley, 1969-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Trojan Horse, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Academic Affairs Faculty Council Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Academic Affairs Faculty Council Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - International Student Affairs Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Lectures Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Membership Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Nominations Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Nominations Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Research Policy and Personnel Faculty Council Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Research Policy and Personnel Faculty Council Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - ROTC Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Student Conduct Committee (Dale E. Lashnit's File) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Student Conduct Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Address to Edmund Ezra Day (several), 1950 (Box 2)
    - AAU Statements on Freedom and Tenure, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom in State Colleges, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure Annual Reports, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure Appointments and Promotions, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure - Basic Legislation, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Boston College - University Status, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - minutes/related materials (5 files), 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 23-27)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Notice of Meetings, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Correspondence - Brown/Malcolm, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Dismissal for Budgetary Reasons, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Dismissal Legislation and Procedures (4 files), 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 31-34)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Disclosures Concerning Students, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Faculty sponsored research, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Finlay File, 1953-1958 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Hofer File, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Honor System, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Kare File, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Membership, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Study of Misfeasance and Nonfeasance, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-1964 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Rights of Students, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Committee on Academic Freedom - Statements of Principle, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Statutes at other schools (4 files), 1945-1958 (Box 2, Folder 46-49)
    - Student Oaths, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Ulric Moore's file, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Collection 11-1-1616 (Box 1-5)
    - Biographical Sketches, Work Papers, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Faculty - Appointments, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Faculty - Mailing Lists, 1970 - June 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Faculty - New Members, Fall 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - General Legislation Work Papers (Folder 1), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - General Legislation Work Papers (Folder 2), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Hourly Wages - Payroll Vouchers (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Approved Housing, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Approved Housing, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Approved Housing Legislation, March 17, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Freshmen (open houses in freshmen Men's living units), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Group Housing Plan, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Housing, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Housing - Student Affairs - Off Campus Housing - Senior Women (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Necrology of the Faculty, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Necrology of the Faculty, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Nominations, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Nominations, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Nominations, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - President Perkins - Princeton Lectures, other speeches (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - President Perkins - Williamsburg-International Conference on World Crisis in Education, Opening Remarks (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom and Responsibility Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Academic Freedom and Policies Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Academic Records and Instruction Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Admissions and Financial Aids Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Calendar and Schedules Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee of the FCR, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Freedom of Teaching and Learning Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - International Student Affairs Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Lectures Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Membership of the University Faculty Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Memorial Statements of the Faculty, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Memorial Statements of the Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Music Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Nominations and Elections Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Personnel Planning and Policy Board, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Physical Education Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Professional & Economic Status of the Faculty Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Research Policies Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Review and Procedures Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - University - ROTC Relationships Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Jack M. Irwin (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Jason W. Mass (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Strom Thurmond (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Academic Freedom and Responsibility Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Academic Programs and Policies Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Academic Records and Instruction Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Budget Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Education Council - June Fessenden-Raden's Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Equilibrium Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee of the FCR, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Financial Aid, Special Committee on, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Freedom of Teaching & Learning Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - International Student Affairs Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Judicial System, Special Committee to Study, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ky Disruption, ad hoc Committe to Study, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Membership Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)